Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 1960 Campaign
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1960
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-012)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-012 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 11, 13, 14
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-013)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-013 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 11, 12, 14
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-014)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-014 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 11, 12, 13
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-015)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-015 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0016, 17, 18, 19
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-016)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-016 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015, 17, 18, 19
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-017)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-017 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015, 16, 18, 19
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-018)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-018 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015, 16, 17, 19
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-019)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-019 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015, 16, 17, 18
    - Button with text: America Needs Nixon, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-020)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-020 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0021
    - Button with text: America Needs Nixon, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-021)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-021 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0020
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: For President Dick Nixon 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-022)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-022 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0023, 24
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: For President Dick Nixon 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-023)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-023 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0022, 24
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: For President Dick Nixon 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-024)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-024 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0022, 23
    - Button with text: Democrats for Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-025)
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-026)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-026 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0027
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-027)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-027 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0026
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-028)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-028 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0029
    - Litho tab with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-029)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-029 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0028
    - Button with text: Greenwich for Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-030)
    - Button with printed photographs of Nixon and Lodge and text: Experience Counts Nixon-Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-031)
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-032)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-032 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0033, 34
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-033)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-033 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0032, 34
    - Button with text: I'm for Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-034)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-034 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0032, 33
    - Button with text: Experience Counts Vote Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-035)
    - Pin with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-036)
    - Pin with clock hands and text: It's time to elect Nixon President, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-037)
    - Republican Committee on Program and Progress Task Force reports, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Bumper sticker/decal: Pat for First Lady, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Campaign memorabilia/souvenir sales literature, samples, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Campaign pamphlets, literature, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Speeches, transcripts, policy pamphlets, 1960 and undated (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Vote Republican, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Nixon for President, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Republican platform, Republican National Convention, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Anti-Kennedy literature, 1960 (Box 15)
    - North Carolina flyers, handouts, and correspondence, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Clippings, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Republican National Committee press releases, publications, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing, 1960
    - Button with text: Stevenson 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES1960-001)
    - Button with printed photograph of Stevenson and text: Stevenson 1960 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES1960-002)
- 1964 Campaign
  - Goldwater, Barry Morris, 1964
    - Pin with text: AuH20, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-001)
    - Pin with text: G, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-002)
    - Matchbook with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: Goldwater in '64, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-003)
      RL-00580-BMG1964-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004
    - Matchbook with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: Goldwater in '65, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-004)
      RL-00580-BMG1964-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 003
    - Pin with text: G Goldwater '64, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-005)
    - Button with text: Goldwater, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-006)
      RL-00580-BMG1964-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007
    - Button with text: Goldwater, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-007)
      RL-00580-BMG1964-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006
    - Pin shaped like eyeglasses, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-008)
    - Button with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: Barry Goldwater Our Next President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-009)
    - Button with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: Goldwater AuH20 for President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-010)
    - Button with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: "In your heart you know he's right" Our Next President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-011)
    - Button with printed photograph of Goldwater and text: Goldwater for President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-012)
    - Button with text: Go with Goldwater and Miller in '64, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-013)
    - Button with text: Goldwater Miller 64, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-014)
    - Campaign flyers, mailings, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Books: "A Choice Not an Echo," by P. Schlafly, and "None Dare Call it Freedom," by J. Stormer, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Goldwater 64, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Au-H20-64, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Campaign literature, platform, Anti-LBJ Young Republican cards, Goldwater pencil, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Poster: Goldwater and Miller, A Choice Not an Echo, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Soda can with text: Goldwater: The Right Drink for Conservative Tastes, 1964 (Box 18, Item RL-00580-BMG1964-015)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1964
    - Button with text: Scientists Engineers Physicians Johnson Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-001)
      RL-00580-LBJ1964-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 11
    - Button with text: Scientists Engineers Physicians Johnson Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-002)
      RL-00580-LBJ1964-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 11
    - Button with text: Scientists Engineers Johnson Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-003)
    - Button with text: LBJ for the USA, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-004)
    - Lenticular button with text: LBJ for the USA, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-005)
    - Button with printed photographs of Johnson and Humphrey and text: Citizens for Johnson & Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-006)
    - Button with printed photograph of Johnson and text: Johnson for President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-007)
    - Litho tab with printed photographs of Johnson and Humphrey and text: Johnson-Humphrey Vote Democratic, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-008)
    - Litho tab with text: Johnson for President, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-009)
    - Litho tab with text: LBJ USA, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-010)
    - Button with text: Johnson and Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-011)
    - Button with text: Scientists Engineers Physicians Johnson Humphrey, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-012)
      RL-00580-LBJ1964-012 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2
    - Matchbook with Lady Bird Special train and plane, with text: Lady Bird Special '64, 1964 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-LBJ1964-013)
    - Campaign literature, North Carolina rally invitations, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Pamphlets, flyers, literature, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Anti-Goldwater clippings, Democratic Party platform, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Scientists and Engineers for Johnson, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Bumper sticker: Scientists/Engineers/Physicians for Johnson/Humphrey, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Bumper sticker: Johnson/Humphrey, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Johnson posters, 1964 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Early Birds for Ladybird poster, Durham, N.C., 1964 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1964
    - Button with text: I'm for Lodge, 1964 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HCL1964-001)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1964
    - Campaign flyers, mailings, 1964 (Box 15)
    - Brochure, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Poster: Rocky can win, 1964 (Oversize-folder 2)
- 1968 Campaign
  - Humphrey, Hubert Horatio, 1968
    - Button with text: Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-001)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3, 4
    - Button with text: Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-002)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 3, 4
    - Button with text: Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-003)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2, 4
    - Button with text: Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-004)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2, 3
    - Button with text: HHH Humphrey, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-005)
    - Button with text: HHH Humphrey, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-006)
    - Button with text: HHH, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-007)
    - Button with printed photograph of Humphrey and text: Humphrey for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-008)
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-009)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-009 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0010, 11, 12
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-010)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-010 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 11, 12
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-011)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-011 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 12
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-012)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-012 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 11
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-013)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-013 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0014, 15, 16
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-014)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-014 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013, 15, 16
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-015)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-015 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013, 14, 16
    - Button with text: Humphrey Muskie, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-016)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-016 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013, 14, 15
    - Pin with text: HHH, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-017)
    - Pin with text: HHH, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-018)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-018 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0019
    - Pin with text: HHH, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-019)
      RL-00580-HHH1968-019 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0018
    - Button with text: HHH Humphrey, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-020)
    - Button with text: HHH, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-HHH1968-021)
    - Bumper sticker: Humphrey/Muskie, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Humphrey, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: HHH Humphrey, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Campaign pamphlets, literature, events, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Placemat, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Duke Committee for Humphrey-Muskie, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Humphry/Muskie plastic sashes, 1968 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Robert Francis, 1968
    - Button with text: RFK, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-RFK1968-001)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1968
    - Campaign literature; Durham Citizens for McCarthy, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1968
    - Republican National Committee materials, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Paulsen, Pat Layton, 1968
    - Button with printed photograph of Paulsen and text: Pat Paulsen for President, 1968 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-PLP19xx-001)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1968
    - Pamphlet, Convention information, campaign literature, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Wallace, George Corley, 1968
    - Button with text: Wallace for President '68, 1968 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-GCW1968-001)
    - Bumper sticker: Wallace in '68, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets, postcard, ephemera, 1968 (Box 16)
- 1972 Campaign
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1972
    - Button with text: Eugene, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-EJM1972-001)
      RL-00580-EJM1972-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3
    - Button with text: Eugene, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-EJM1972-002)
      RL-00580-EJM1972-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 3
    - Button with text: Eugene, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-EJM1972-003)
      RL-00580-EJM1972-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2
    - Button with text: McCarthy, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-EJM1972-004)
  - McGovern, George Stanley, 1972
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-001)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3, 4
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-002)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 3, 4
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-003)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2, 4
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-004)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001, 2, 3
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-005)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 7
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-006)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 7
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-007)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 6
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-008)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-008 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-009)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-009 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 008
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-010)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-010 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0011, 12
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-011)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-011 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0010, 12
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-012)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-012 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0010, 11
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-013)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-013 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0014, 15
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-014)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-014 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013, 15
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-015)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-015 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013, 14
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-016)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-016 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0017
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-017)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-017 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0016
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-018)
    - Button with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-019)
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-020)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-020 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0021
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-021)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-021 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0020
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-022)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-022 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0023
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-023)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-023 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0022
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-024)
    - Button with text: McGovern Shriver Citizen Power, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-025)
    - Button with text: McGovern Million Member Club: I Belong How About You?, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-026)
    - Button with color drawing of McGovern and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-027)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-027 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0028, 29
    - Button with color drawing of McGovern and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-028)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-028 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0027, 29
    - Button with color drawing of McGovern and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-029)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-029 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0027, 28
    - Button with color photograph of McGovern and text: George McGovern for President, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-030)
    - Button with rainbow and text: Together with McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-031)
    - Button with rainbow and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-032)
    - Button with text: McGovern President '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-033)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-033 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0034, 35
    - Button with text: McGovern President '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-034)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-034 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0033, 35
    - Button with text: McGovern President '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-035)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-035 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0033, 34
    - Button with text: Me & McG, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-036)
    - Button with Greek symbol for women and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-037)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-037 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0038, 39
    - Button with Greek symbol for women and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-038)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-038 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0037, 39
    - Button with Greek symbol for women and text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-039)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-039 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0037, 38
    - Button with text: McGovern & Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-040)
    - Button with text: McG, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-041)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-041 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0042, 43
    - Button with text: McG, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-042)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-042 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0041, 43
    - Button with text: McG, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-043)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-043 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0041, 42
    - Button with donkey and text: McGovern Shriver 72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-044)
    - Button with text: McGovern '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-045)
    - Pin with text: McG, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-046)
    - Pin with text: McGovern '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-047)
    - Button with text: McG '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-048)
    - Button with text: McGovern for President, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-049)
    - Lenticular button with photograph of McGovern and text: McGovern for President in '72, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-050)
    - Patch with rainbow and text: McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-051)
    - Patch with text: McGovern for President, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-052)
    - Button with text: Viva McGovern Shriver, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-053)
    - Button with text: Majority for a Silent Agnew, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-054)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-054 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0055
    - Button with text: Majority for a Silent Agnew, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-055)
      RL-00580-GSM1972-055 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0054
    - Litho tab with text: McGovern, 1972 (Box 7, Item RL-00580-GSM1972-056)
    - Bumper sticker: McGovern '72, 1972 (Box 16)
    - North Carolina campaign recruitment, pamphlets, and literature, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Newspaper advertisement: North Carolina Needs a Democrat, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Muskie, Edmund Sistus, 1972
    - Button with text: Muskie!, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-ESM1972-001)
      RL-00580-ESM1972-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002
    - Button with text: Muskie!, 1972 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-ESM1972-002)
      RL-00580-ESM1972-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1972
    - Button with text: Senior Power for the President, 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-001)
    - Button with text: Young Voters for the President, 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-002)
    - Button with printed photograph of Nixon and text: Nixon for President, 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-003)
    - Button with printed photographs of Nixon and Agnew with text: The Winning Team 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-004)
      RL-00580-RMN1972-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005
    - Button with printed photographs of Nixon and Agnew with text: The Winning Team 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-005)
      RL-00580-RMN1972-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004
    - Button with text: President Nixon. Now more than ever., 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-006)
      RL-00580-RMN1972-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007
    - Button with text: President Nixon. Now more than ever., 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-007)
      RL-00580-RMN1972-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006
    - Pin with elephant and text: Nixon in '72, 1972 (Box 6, Item RL-00580-RMN1972-008)
    - Bumper sticker: President Nixon. Now more than ever, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Bumper sticker: Nixon Agnew, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Pamphlets, Republican platforms, contribution requests, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Anti-Nixon literature, 1972 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Sanford, James Terry, 1972
    - Button with text: Terry Sanford, 1972 (Box 8, Item RL-00580-JTS1972-001)
- 1976 Campaign